=The Shoufu Can Read Mind=
= الشوفو يستطيع قراءة العقل =
=Episode 16=
= الحلقة 16 =
(Wanren Pavilion)
(جناح وانرين)
Interesting.
(جناح وانرين) ممتع.
It's interesting.
(جناح وانرين) إنه ممتع.
(Wanren Pavilion)
(جناح وانرين)
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
why did you...
لماذا فعلت...
Why did I try to kill the Grand Secretariat
لماذا حاولت قتل الأمانة العامة
on the street?
في الشارع؟
Zhou Kaiping
تشو كايبينغ
has been punished and executed for the imperial examination case,
تمت معاقبته وإعدامه في قضية الامتحان الإمبراطوري ،
but Xu Yanqing is still investigating.
لكن شو يانكينغ لا يزال يحقق.
He's even suspecting me now.
حتى أنه يشك بي الآن.
I have to teach him a lesson.
علي أن أعلمه درسا.
Ouyang Yu,
أويانغ يو ،
don't forget.
لا تنسى.
When I sent you to Xu Yanqing's side,
عندما أرسلتك إلى جانب Xu Yanqing ،
I wanted you to get Xu Yanqing on my side
كنت أريدك أن تجعل شو يانكينغ إلى جانبي
to help me.
لتساعدني.
Are you in love with him now?
هل أنت مغرم به الآن؟
I...
أنا...
I know that
وأنا أعلم ذلك
Xu Yanqing is a reliable man,
شو يانكينغ رجل جدير بالثقة ،
but don't forget that
لكن لا تنسى ذلك
he's a minister and I'm a prince.
هو وزير وأنا أمير.
No matter how much authority Xu Yanqing has,
بغض النظر عن مدى سلطة Xu Yanqing ،
he's just a servant that I can kill any time.
إنه مجرد خادم يمكنني قتله في أي وقت.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Physician,
الطبيب المعالج،
how is it?
كيف هذا؟
Is he going to die?
هل سيموت؟
Although the arrow didn't hit his organs,
على الرغم من أن السهم لم يصطدم بأعضائه ،
his wound has become black.
أصبح جرحه أسود.
It means the arrow was poisonous.
هذا يعني أن السهم كان سامًا.
I'm not too confident.
لست واثقا جدا.
Please, physician.
من فضلك أيها الطبيب.
Please save him.
الرجاء حفظه.
I'm a physician.
انا طبيب.
Of course I'd try my best.
بالطبع سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
Physician.
الطبيب المعالج.
I've done
لقد فعلت
everything that I could.
كل ما استطعت.
Now,
الآن،
we'll have to wait for three days
علينا الانتظار لمدة ثلاثة أيام
and see if he could make it.
ونرى ما إذا كان يمكنه فعل ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
(Didn't the book say that you're evil?)
(ألم يقل الكتاب أنك شرير؟)
(But why did you risk your life to save me?)
(لكن لماذا خاطرت بحياتك لإنقاذي؟)
(Could it be)
(هل من الممكن ذلك)
(the book was wrong?)
(هل كان الكتاب خاطئًا؟)
I'm warning you.
أنا أحذرك.
Don't go crazy.
لا تصاب بالجنون.
(Xu Yanqing.)
(شو يانكينغ.)
(Which one is the real you?)
(أيهما حقيقي؟)